<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Apurva Khatri</title>
    <link>https://apurvakhatri.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Apurva Khatri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 23:41:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://apurvakhatri.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Making decision to go right or left with Binary Search.</title>
      <link>https://apurvakhatri.com/posts/makingrightleftdecision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 23:41:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apurvakhatri.com/posts/makingrightleftdecision/</guid>
      <description>Making decision to go right or left with Binary Search. This post will be discussing approaches to certain problems which strictly teaches binary search.
I will not be presenting any solutions just discussing the approaches.
Single Element in Sorted Array Description: You are given a sorted array consisting of only integers where every element appears exactly twice, except for one element which appears exactly once.
Return the single element that appears only once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://apurvakhatri.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apurvakhatri.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Apurva Khatri (Ah-poor-vah Khuh-tree), currently pursuing a Master of Science in Computer Science at Northeastern University. With approximately three years of experience as a software developer, I specialize in designing and implementing robust solutions across various technologies and platforms.
Professional Background I have 2.8 years of experience as a Software Developer at ICICI Lombard, a leading general insurance company in India. During my time there, I played a pivotal role in:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://apurvakhatri.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apurvakhatri.com/resume/</guid>
      <description> Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Page: / </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ServerLess LLM Application</title>
      <link>https://apurvakhatri.com/projects/serverlessllmapplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apurvakhatri.com/projects/serverlessllmapplication/</guid>
      <description>Exploring how Amazon Bedrock and serverless architecture were used to automate customer call summarization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
